CONTACT

+33 7 48 15 50 87

Lyon, France

<u>jeromecornu02@gmail.com</u>







KEY SKILLS

Technical

- Unity (C#), Unreal Engine (Blueprints & C++)
- Al / behavior trees, level scripting, prototyping
- UX readability & feedback, mechanics balancing
- Git, Perforce, Jira, Trello, Miro

Soft

- Teamwork & Collaboration
- Problem-Solving
- Autonomy & Self-Management
- Positive Team Spirit

EDUCATION

2021 - 2024
GAMING CAMPUS (LYON, FR)

- MSc Specialized Game Developer
- Valedictorian 2023

2024 FREE CANDIDATE

 Master IT – Intelligent Applications & Big Data

2019 - 2021 IUT VALENCE (VALENCE, FR)

• DUT in Computer Science

LANGUAGES

English - C1 (CLES B2 2020)

French - Native

Spanish - A1

JÉRÔME CORNU

PROGRAMMER

PROFILE

Unity developer (C#) with additional experience in Unreal Engine (Blueprints & C++), with exposure to game design principles. Experienced in prototyping mechanics, collaborating, and building gameplay systems.

Proactive, communicative, and comfortable iterating on features based on player feedback. Passionate about bridging design and tech to improve the player experience.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Game Developer - MathsAndGo

2023 - 2024

Apprenticeship (Remote)

- Designed and developed 3 educational games using TypeScript (Phaser) for primary school audiences.
- Contributed to gameplay ideation, mechanics definition, and core loop structuring.
- Implemented AI behaviors and responsive UI systems adapted to children's interactions.

Gameplay Programmer - Pôle Prod

2022 - 2023

Apprenticeship (Le Soler, FR)

- Developped mechanics in Unreal Engine 4 and 5 (Blueprints).
- Developed AI behavior, combat mechanics, and progression features.
- Automated Unreal Engine data workflows via Excel to improve character customization system.
- Wrote and maintained documentation for designers, 3D artists and programmers.

Game Projects - Gaming Campus

2021 - 2024

Academic Project-Based Learning (Lyon, FR)

- Completed 20 group projects covering full-cycle game development.
- Took charge of all aspects of development: mechanics, systems, UI, AI, level scripting, iteration, multiplayer...
- Developed games across various genres using Unity and Unreal: FPS, puzzle, management, platformer, infiltration, etc.
- Participated in UX and mission layout improvements based on player feedback (Indie Game Lyon FR - 2022).

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Board game designer (Andor expansions, Cthulhu Wars)
- School ambassador, Member of campus association (2021 2022)
- Competitive tennis player (rank 15/5)
- Driver's license (B)

